Guide to the Rochambeau Papers and Rochambeau Family Cartographic Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Map Collection of the Marquis de Rochambeau, 1669-1743; Series IV
  - MISCELLANEOUS MAPS
    - IK 281 Battle of Parma. Paris., 1734
      Title and/or other information taken from map: PLAN DU COMBAT/DE/PARME/Donné le 29. Juin 1734/ou l'Armée des deux/Couronnes à batue celle/de l'Empereur./DÉDIÉ AU ROY/ Par son très humble, très/obeissant Serviteur et Sujet,/ le P. PLACIDE Augustin/Déchaussé, et Geographe/Ordinaire de Sa Majesté. [and] A PARIS/Se vend par Michel Buquet Portier des Augus=/tins Déchaussés de la place des Victoires./Avec privilege de Sa Majesté pour 15. ans/ 1734./le Parmentier Sculp.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 15 5/16 x 19 7/16 inches.
      SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 42, folder 659.
    - IK 163 Map of the States Situated on the Moselle and the Rhine. Paris: G. Danet.
      Map tab inscription: Allemagne/(la Moselle,/le Rhin et/ la Saare)/IK/163.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE/ PARTICULIERE/DUNE GRANDE/PARTIE DES ETATS/SITUEZ SUR/LA MOSELLE/LE RHEIN/ET LA SAARRE/Dressée et Dediée A Monsieur le/Marêchal duc de VILLARS/a Paris chez G. Danet gendre de/l'auteur Sur le pont N. Dame a la/Sphere Royale avec privilege
      Notes: Colored. 27 5/8 x 21 5/8 inches.
      SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 42, folder 660.
    - IK 398 Map of Peru and Brazil. Paris: Guillaume de L'Isle., 1703
      Map tab inscription: Perou, Brésil
      Inscribed on map: IK/398./Perou Bresil/Pays des amazonnes [and] perou bresil et pay de amasonnes/isle de Ceylan en asie
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE/ DE LA TERRE FERME/DU PEROU, DU BRESIL/ET DU PAYS DES AMAZONES/Dressée sur les Descriptions de Herrera/de Laet, et des P P. d'Acuña, et M. Rodriguéz/et sur plusieurs Relations et/Observations posterieures/Par Guillaume Del'Isle Geographe/de l'Academie Royale des Sciences/A PARIS/Chéz l'Auteur Rue des Canettes pres/de St. Sulpice avec Privilege du Roy/pour 20. ans 1703.
      Notes: Colored. 19 x 26 13/16 inches.
      SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 42, folder 661.
    - IK 399 Paraguay and Chile. Paris: Guillaume de L'Isle., 1703
      Map tab inscription: Paraguay/Chili
      Inscribed on map: IK/399./Paragauy Chily [and] [P]araguay du chily [and] Le paraguai du chily
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE/DU PARAGUAY/DU CHILI/DU DETROIT DE MAGELLAN &c./Dressée sur les Descriptions/des P P. Alfonse d'Ovalle, et Nicolas Techo,/et sur les Relations et memoires/de Brouwer, Narbouroug, Mr. de Beauchesne &c./Par GUILLAUME DE L'ISLE Geographe/de l'Academie Royale des Sciences/A PARIS/Chéz l'Auteur, Rue des Canettes préz de St. Sulpice/avec Privilege du Roi pour 20 ans/1703./Gravée par Liebaux le fils
      Notes: Colored. 19 3/4 x 26 5/8 inches.
      SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 42, folder 662.
- Map Collection of the Comte de Rochambeau, 1695-1792; Series V; 5.25; (13 boxes)
  Series V, Map Collection of the Comte de Rochambeau, is organized into ten subseries: War of the Austrian Succession, Cantons of Franche-Comté and Campaign against Mandrin, Seven Years' War, Inspector-General of the Infantry, Plan to Invade England, American Revolution, Command of Picardy and Artois, Command of Alsace, Journey to Switzerland, and Army of the North: Brabant Campaign.
  - WAR OF THE AUSTRIAN SUCCESSION
    - Bohemian and Bavarian Campaigns
      - IK 251 Bohemia. Paris: Le Rouge. (Box 7, Folder 319-327)
        This map is divided into 9 parts. There are 3 sections of 3 pieces each. Each map is uncolored, and 8 x 6 inches, folded.
        These maps were cased together in a green board sleeve. See also: Oversize Sleeve Boxes, box 51.
        1) Map tab inscription on part 1: Boheme le flle./Bôheme 1e flle haut/IK/251.
        Notes to map, part 1: This is the first piece in the first section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 5/8 X 22 3/8 inches.
        2) Map tab inscription on part 2: Boheme [rest illegible]/ Bôheme 2e flle haut
        Notes to map, part 2: This is the second piece in the first section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 5/8 X 22 1/4 inches.
        3) Map tab inscription on part 3: Boheme 3e [rest illegible] Boheme. 3e flle haut
        Notes to map, part 3: This is the third piece in the first section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 5/8 X 22 5/16 inches.
        4) Map tab inscription on part 4: Boheme 4 flle M/Boheme. 4e flle Milieu
        Notes to map, part 4: This is the first piece in the second section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 1/4 x 22 7/16 inches.
        5) Map tab inscription on part 5: Boheme 5e flle [rest illegible]/Boheme. 5e flle Milieu
        Notes to map, part 5: This is the second piece in the second section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 1/4 x 22 5/16 inches.
        6) Map tab inscription on part 6: [illegible]/Boheme. 6e flle Milieu
        Notes to map, part 6: This is the third piece in the second section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 3/8 X 22 5/16 inches.
        7) Map tab inscription on part 7: [illegible]/Boheme. 7e flle Bas.
        Notes to map, part 7: This is the first piece in the third section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 7/16 X 22 7/16 inches.
        8) Map tab inscription on part 8: [illegible]/Boheme. 8e flle Bas.
        Notes to map, part 8: This is the second piece in the third section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 7/16 X 22 3/8 inches.
        9) Map tab inscription on part 9: [illegible]/Boheme. 9e flle Bas.
        Title and/or other information taken from map, part 9: CARTE/CHOROGRAPHIQUE/DE LA/BOHEME/Divisée en 12 Cercles/ Avec le Comté de Glatz/et le Territoire d'Egra/En neuf Feuilles égalles aux vingt cinq Petittea/de l'Illustre MULLER/DEDIÉE/A:S:AS.M. LE COMTE DE CLERMONT/PRINCE/Par son très humble et très Obéissant/Serviteur Le Rouge Ingr. Géographe./A PARIS,/Chez l'Auteur rue des Grands Augustins/ vis à vis le Panier fleuri/M.DCC.LVII./Avec Privilége du Roy.
        Notes to map, part 9: This is the third piece in the third section of 3 pieces (left to right). Linen-backed. Uncolored. 19 5/16 x 22 1/4 inches.
      - IK 238 County of Glatz. Nuremberg: Homann Erben., 1747 (Box 7, Folder 328)
        Map tab inscription: Glatz
        Inscribed on paper laid down on map: IK/238./Glatz.
        Title and/or other information taken from map: COMITATUS/ GLACIENSIS/Tabula Geogr./Ex autographis delineationibus/ depromta/Edentibus Homannianis/Heredibus/A 1747. [and] LA COMTE DE GLATZ avec le Principautè de MVNSTERBERG, dressèe sur des dessins Autographes/par Tob. Meyer aux depans des Heritiers de Homann à Nüremberg. 1747.
        Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 22 1/8 x 23 1/2 inches overall, 7 1/2 x 4 1/2 inches folded.
      - IK 210 Electorate of Hanover. Amsterdam: Covens and Mortier., 1745
        Inscribed on map: Electorat d'Hannovre/IK/210. [and] illegible inscription on another section
        Title and/or other information taken from map: L'ELECTORAT/DE HANNOVER/ou les Domaines/DU ROI/DE LA GRANDE/BRETAGNE/EN/ALLEMAGNE./a Amsterdam/Chez/COVENS et MORTIER./1745. [and] ELECTORATUS HANOVERANUS SIVE DOMINIA REGIS MAGNAE BRITTANNIAE IN GERMANIA
        Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 24 1/4 x 20 5/8 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 663.
      - IK 250 Kingdom of Bohemia. Paris: Le Rouge., 1742
        Inscribed on map: Royaume de boheme - muller/Le Rouge/ IK/250 [and] boheme [and] Bas rentres (?)
        Title and/or other information taken from map: LE ROYAUME/DE/BOHEME/Carte Reduite/Sur celle de 25 Feuilles/ Faite à Prague./PAR MÜLLER/A PARIS./Par et chez le Sieur le/Rouge Ingr. Géographe/du Roy rue des Grands/Augustins vis à vis/le Panier Fleury./A.P.D.R./1742
        Notes: Colored. 23 1/8 x 32 3/16 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadside Case, folder 822.
      - IK 211 Duchy of Magdeburg. Nuremberg: Johann Baptist Homann., n.d.
        Inscribed on map: IK/2ll./Allemagne/Duchè de Magdebourg
        Title and/or other information taken from map: SAXONIAE TRACTUS/DUCATUM MAGDEBUR-/GENSEM cum suo CIRCULO SALICO/ PRINC:ANHALTINUM HALBERSTADI-/ENSEM finitimarumq Regionum ELECTO-/RATUS nempe BRANDENBURG:SAXONIAE/DUCATUS BRUNSVICENSIS etc. Partes/Ostendens/editus/a Ioh:Baptist: Homani S.C.M.Geog./Filio/NORIBERGAE
        Notes: Colored. 18 7/8 x 25 15/16 inches
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 664
      - IK 205 Electorate of Hanover. Paris: Le Rouge., 1741
        Map tab inscription: 1741/Hanovre/IK/205.
        Inscribed on map: electorat d'hanovre
        Title and/or other information taken from map: L'ELECTORAT DE HANNOVER/ou se trouvent les Camps et les Plans des principales Villes de cette Province et de l'Eveché de Hildesheim qui y est enclavé/Par le Sr. le ROUGE jngenieur Geographe du ROY rue des grands Augustins vis a vis le Panier Fleuri 1741.
        Notes: Colored. 23 1/2 x 33 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadsize Case, folder 823.
      - IK 215 Duchy of Wurtemberg. Nuremberg: Johann Baptist Homann., n.d.
        Map tab inscription: Wurtemberg/Carte allemande
        Inscribed on map: [Wur]temberg [covered over by map tab; and] IK/215.
        Title and/or other information taken from map: DUCATUS/ WURTENBERGICI/cum Locis limitaneis,/utpote maxima parte CIRCULI SUEVICI/praesertim Utroq MARCHIONATU BADN/SI et SYLVA vulgo NIGRA,/Niva et post omnes exactissima Deline /per/M. IOHANNEM MAJER/Pastorem Walddorssensem/opera/ IOH. BAPTISTAE HOMANNI/Noribergae/Cum Privilegio S.C.M.
        Notes: Colored. 22 3/4 x 19 3/8 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 665.
      - IK 218 Bavaria. Nuremberg: Johann Baptist Homann., 1728
        Inscribed on map: baviere [and] IK/21
        Title and/or other information taken from map: BAVARIAE/ CIRCULUS et ELECTORAT/IN SUAS QUASQUE DITIONES/tam cum/ ADIACENTIBUS. QUAM INSERTIS/REGIONIBUS/accuratissime divisus/per/IO: BAPTISTAM HOMANNUM/Norimbergae./1728 [and] Cum Privilegio Sac. Caes. Majestatis
        Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 22 1/8 x 19 1/4 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 666.
      - IK 185 Westphalia. Paris: Le Rouge., 1742
        Map tab inscription: 1742/Westphalie/IK/185.
        Title and/or other information taken from map: LA WESTPHALIE/Suivant les dernieres/observations/de Homann et de/Hubener./A PARIS/Par et chez le/Sr. le Rouge Ingr. /et Geographe du/Roy rue des Grads/Augustins 1742/ A.P.D.R.
        Notes: Colored. 31 7/8 x 23 1/8 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadsize Case, folder 824.
      - IK 255 The Environs of Gaslau. Homann Erben., 1742
        Inscribed on map: IK/255. [and] bataill de czazlau [and] Bohême
        Title and/or other information taken from map: Les Environs de Czaslau avec le Plan de la Bataille d. 17 May 1742. entre les Autrichiens & les Prussiens./ad No. 21. Erlang: Zeit:/Extr: [and] Schlacht der Oesterr: u. Preussen bey Czaslau der Hauptst: im Czaslauer Kr: im Königr: Böhmen. zufinden bey den Homännischen Erben. 1742
        Notes: Colored. 12 1/16 x 14 7/16 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 667.
      - IK 253 Plan of Prague. Paris: Le Rouge., 1742
        Map tab inscription: Prague/IK/253.
        Inscribed on map: Prague [and] plan de prague
        Title and/or other information taken from map: PLAN/Des Environs/DE PRAGUE/Et des Camps/des deux Armées/DEDIÉ/A Mgr. le Prince/de Soubise/Par son trés humble et trés/ Obeissant Serviteur le Rouge./A PARIS./Rue des Augustins/ vis-a-vis le Panier/Fleury, 1742. [and] PLAN/DE/PRAGUE/ .../avec Privilege du Roi. suivant l'Original envoyé par Mgr. le Prince de Soubise.
        Notes: Uncolored. 20 5/8 x 27 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 668.
      - IK 65 The Duchies of Lorraine and of Bar. Paris: Le Rouge., 1743
        Inscribed on map: IK/65. [and] lorraine [and] Le Rouge
        Title and/or other information taken from map: LES DUCHÉS/DE LORRAINE/ET DE BAR/LES EVECHÉS DE METZ TOUL/ ET VERDUN/DEDIÉS/à Mgr. le Comte de Maurepas/Par son trés humble et tres Obeissant/Serviteur le Rouge Ingr. Géographe/du Roy/A PARIS/Rue des Grands Augustins/1743.
        Notes: Colored. 19 3/4 x 25 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 669.
      - IK 67 Map of Nice and Villefranche. Paris: Guerard.
        Inscribed on map: IK/67.[and]carte des environs de Nice ville franche/Depuis Villeneuve en provence jusqu'a Monaco.
        Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE Particuliere des Environs de/NICE, et de VILLE-FRANCHE, depuis Ville-neuve/en Provence, jusqu'à Monaco./Ou l'on voit la Marche des Armées de France et d'Espagne, leurs/ passage du Var, et les différentes attaques des retranchements de/Mont-Alban et de Ville-franche. le 19. Avril 1744. [and] A Paris Chez le Sr. Guerard Graveur rue St. Jacques proche St. Yves au Chariot d'Or. Et Chez le Sr. Dheulland rue Serpente attenant l'Hôtel de la Serpente Chez Mr. Martin Officier du Roy.
        Notes: Uncolored. 23 5/16 x 31 5/8 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadside Case, folder 825.
      - IK 69 Duchy of Luxembourg. Paris: Crépy., n.d.
        Map tab inscription: Luxembourg/IK/69.
        Inscribed on map: Duché de Luxembourg [and] Luxembourg
        Title and/or other information taken from map: LE DUCHE DE/LUXEMBOURG/Partie de le Archeveché et/Electorat de TREVES, Electora/PALATIN du RHIN, Archeveché/et Electora de MAYENCE,/Partie de LIMBOURG, duché/de DEUX PONTS, de la LORRAINE,/Pays MAIS SAIN, cour des/Rivierre de Sar, de la MOZELLE,/et de la MEUSE &c./.../Lieues communes d'Allemagne/a Paris chez Crepy rue S. Jacques a l'Image S. Pierre
        Notes: Colored. 23 1/8 x 32 1/2 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadside Case, folder 826.
      - IK 249 Theater of War in Bohemia. Paris: Le Rouge., 1741
        Map tab inscription: Boheme/IK/249.
        Inscribed on map: -1756 D- [and] Theatre De la guerre En Boheme
        Title and/or other information taken from map: THEATRE DE LA GUERRE/EN BOHEME/avec les pri[n]cipaux Postes de ce Royaume/A PARIS/Par et Chez le Sr. le Rouge Ingr. Geogphe. du Roy rue des/grands Augustins vis a vis le panier fleuri .../1741.
        Notes: Colored. 23 1/8 x 31 3/4 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadside Case, folder 827.
      - IK 278 Piedmont Valleys of Durance and Briançon.
        Inscribed on map: IK/278. [and] Piémont/Vallée de la Durance et Brianconhais - [and] Vallés du roy d Sardaigne. Frontieres (?) de briancon [and] on map front in Rochambeau's hand "X/X/Chemin que l'on peut/pratiquer avec le canon"
        Title and/or other information taken from map: Partie Du Piemont [and] Vallée De Névache [and] Vallée Du Monestier [and] Vallée de Serviere [and] Val-louise [and] Embrunois [and] Gresivaudan
        Notes: Watercolor. 21 1/2 x 35 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadside Case, folder 828.
      - IK 160 German War., 1753
        Inscribed on map: Guerre d'Allemagne,/IK/160. [and] 1736/1753
        Title and/or other information taken from map: NEUE/ CHURSAECHSISCHE/POST CHARTE/...auch Geogr: u: der Kon: Preuse:Soc:der Wissensch, Mittgl,/1736./aufs neue revidirt/1753.
        Notes: This the left hand portion of a larger map. Uncolored. 26 1/4 x 20 5/8 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 670.
      - IK 154 The Area surrounding the Rhine below Speyer near Mayence. Nuremberg: Homann Erben.
        Inscribed on map: cours du rhin et le bergstrass/de spire a mayence/IK/154.
        Title and/or other information taken from map: Die Gegenden des Rheins/von/SPEYER biss MAYNTZ/nebst der Situation laengst/der Bergstrasse/zwischen dem Rhein und dem Odewaldt,/dem Mayn und Necker. 1735./Imverlag/ Der Homaennischen Erben./Mit Kaysallergn. Privil. [and] Les Environs du Rhin, depuis Spire jusqu'à Mayence, avec les pais adjacents de la Rue des Montagnes appellée BERG- STRASSE/ entre les Rivieres du Rhin, de Main, & de Neckar. Par & chez les Heritiers de Homan à Norimberg.
        Notes: Colored. 21 7/8 x 42 3/4 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Rolled Maps, folder 894.
      - IK 254 Plan of Prague. Paris., n.d.
        Map tab inscription: 25 décembre/1741/Plan de Prague/ IK/254.
        Inscribed on map: plan de prague
        Title and/or other information taken from map: PLAN DE PRAGUE/Capital du Royaume de Boheme prise par l'armée de France, de Bavierre, et de Saxe. la nuit du 25 au 26 Décemb 1741/Ou l'on a marqué exactement les Retranchements que Mrs. les Mareschaux de BROGLE et de BELLISLE ont fait pour la/déffence de cette place contre les entreprises de L'armée Autrichienne; ou l'on voit le nom des regiments tant Dragons/Cavallerie qu'Infanterie et Husard qui Composent nôtre Armé sous le Canon de cette Ville le tout gravée sur le/dessein levée au Camp de Prague, tout nouvellement/A PARIS Chez l'Auteur rue St. Jacques vis avis la Fontaine St. Severin à la Providence/ Et chez le Sr. Nolin Géographe rue St. Jacques à l'enseigne de la Place des Victoires et le Sr. Humblot rue St. Jacques a l'enfant jesus [and] Baieul le jeune excud et Sculp.
        Notes: Colored. 27 1/8 x 20 1/2 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 671.
      - IK 256 New Plan of Prague and Environs. Paris: Bailleul.
        Map tab inscription: Prague/et/environs/IK/256.
        Inscribed on map: Allemagne et Environs [?] de prague
        Title and/or other information taken from map: NOUVEAU PLAN DE LA VILLE/DE PRAGUE/Et de ses Environs, Capitale de Bohème Assie=/-gée par les Autrichiens sous les ordres de Mr. le/Prince Charles de Loraine, deffendue par l'Ar-/-mée des François commandée par Mr. le Ma=/rechale de Broglie le, 4 Aoust 1742, Avec la/liste et le Campement des Regiment François et/Autrichiens, tans Infanterie, Dragons, que/Cavalerie [and] APARIS/Chez Le Sr. Baillieul/ Lainé Geographe a/Graveur du Roy Place/Maubert au coin de la/rue Perdu./Et chez Charles An=/-toine Jombert Librai/=re du Roy pour l'Ar=/tillerie et le Genie quay/des Augustin au coin/de la rue Gillecoeur.
        Notes: Colored. 20 1/2 x 27 3/16 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 672.
      - IK 257 Hungary. Nuremberg: Johann Baptist Homann., n.d.
        Map tab inscription: Hongrie/IK/257.
        Inscribed on map: Carte De hongrie
        Title and/or other information taken from map: REGNI/ HUNGARIAE/Tabula Generalis/ex Archetypo MÜLLERIANO S C M. Capit et Ingr/de sumta, et in hane formam contraeta/viis Veredariis aucta, / ? ? Pacis Passarovicensis Confinus illustrata/a/IO. BAPT. HOMANNO/ Sac. Caes. Maj. Geographo/ Norimbergae. [and] Cum Privilegio Sacrae Caesareae Majestatis.
        Notes: Colored. 21 1/2 x 24 7/8 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 673.
      - IK 152 The Course of the Rhine. Paris: Guillaume de L'Isle., 1704
        This map is divided into 3 parts which connect bottom to top.
        1) No map tab on part 1
        Title and/or other information taken from map, part 1: LE COURS DU RHIN au dessus de Strasbourg, et les Païs adjacens. Par Guill. de l'Isle, de l'Academ. Rle. des Sciences. [and] A Paris chez l'Auteur rue des Canettes/ prez St. Sulpice avec Privilege 1704.
        Notes to map, part 1: Colored. 20 1/2 x 27 5/8 inches.
        2) Map tab inscription on part 2: -- [part of tab missing [c]ours du Rhin/depuis Strasbourg/IK/152.
        Title and/or other information taken from map, part 2: LE COURS DU RHIN depuis Strasbourg jusqu'a Worms ET LES PAYS ADJACENS [and] Par Guillaume Del 'Isle Geogs. de l'Academie Royale des/Sciences A Paris chéz l'Auteur Rue des Canettes pres de S. Sulpice avec Priv [and] Desrosiers Sculpt.
        Notes to map, part 2: Colored. 20 3/4 x 27 1/2 inches.
        3) No map tab on part 3
        Title and/or other information taken from map, part 3: LE COURS DU RHIN depuis Worms, jusqua Bonne, ET LES PAYS ADJACE[N]S [and] Par Guillaume Del'Isle Geographe de l'Academie Royale des Sciences/avec Privilege du Roy pour 20. ans.1704.
        Notes to map, part 3: Colored. 20 13/16 x 27 11/16 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folders 674-676
      - IK 245 Map of Germany., 1710
        Inscribed on map: IK/245./245 [and] Allemagne/Partie de l'allemagne opposée/à l'Alsace [and] Wurtemburg
        Title and/or other information taken from map: DOMS/ Serenissimo Colsissimoq. Principi ae Domino Domino/ EBERHARDO LUDOVICO/Duci Würtenbergiae et Thecciae,/ Comiti Montis belgardi, Dynastae in Haydenheim &c/Sac. Caes. Maj. ae Rom. Imp ut et Circuli Sueviei Gene/rali Mareschalls Campi e-Generali Equitatus &c/Domino suo Clementissimo/Tabulam hanc in debitae Submissionis tesseram/Seutter/Año 1710
        Notes: Colored. 26 5/16 x 22 5/8 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadside Case, folder 829.
    - Low Countries Campaign
      - IK 170 Duchies of Cleves and Juliers. Paris.
        Inscribed on map: Duches de Cleves et/de Juliers/partie meridionale/IK/170/mageldorf
        Title and/or other information taken from map: A PARIS, Chez l'Auteur, joignant les grands Augustins, aux 2. Globes, avec Privilége
        Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 18 5/8 x 28 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 677.
      - IK 113 Detailed Map of the Environs of Namur, Charleroi, Dinant, etc. Paris: Crépy., 1743
        Map tab inscription: 1743/Environs de/Namur, Char-/leroy, Dinant/etc/IK/113.
        Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE PARTICULIERE DES ENVIRONS DE NAMUR CHARLEROY DINANT PHILIPEVILLE ROCROY CHARLEMONT GIVET &c [and] a Paris Chez Crepy rue S. Jacques a limage S. Pierre [and] 1743 [and] Dressé sur les Memoires de Eugenes Henry Friex
        Notes: Uncolored. 23 1/16 x 31 1/16 inches
        SEE: Oversize Broadside Case, folder 830.
      - IK 140 Battle Won by the King at Lawfeld on 2 July 1747. Paris: Le Rouge., n.d.
        Map tab inscription: 1747/Bataille de/Laveld/IK/140.
        Inscribed on map: La Marche, the name of Rochambeau's regiment, and the place where he was wounded.
        Title and/or other information taken from map: BATAILLE/ Gagnée/Par le Roy/A LAVELDT,/le 2. Juillet 1747./A PARIS /Chez le Rouge/rue des Augustins.
        Notes: Colored. 16 3/8 x 21 3/16 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 678.
      - IK 119 Plan of Maastricht and of Fort St. Pierre. Paris: Le Rouge., 1747
        Inscribed on map: maestrick/Plan de Mastrick/IK/ll9.
        Title and/or other information taken from map: PLAN/DE MAESTRICHT/du Fort St. Pierre/avec les nouveaux ouvrages projetes/A PARIS,/chez le Sr. le Rouge/Ingénieur Géographe du Roy,/rue des grands Augustins/Déc. 1747.
        Notes: Uncolored. 22 11/16 x 27 3/8 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Broadside Case, folder 831.
      - IK 120 Environs of Maastricht. Brussels: George Friex., n.d.
        Inscribed on map: mastrict/IK/120
        Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE PARTICULIERE DES ENVIRONS DE MAESTRICHT, PARTIE DE LIEGE FAUCQUEMONT, ET PAYS D'OUTRE-MEUSE. [and] A Bruxelle chez George Friex Imprimeur de Sa Majesté rue de la maders (?)
        Notes: Linen-backed. Uncolored. 16 3/8 x 21 15/16 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 679.
      - IK 139 Middelburg in Holland. Paris: Le Rouge.
        Map tab inscription: Middelbourg/(Hollande)/IK/139.
        Inscribed on map: Middelbourg
        Title and/or other information taken from map: MIDDELBOURG/EN ZEELANDE/a Paris/Chez le Sr. le Rouge rue/des Augustins
        Notes: Uncolored. 15 3/4 x 23 inches.
        SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 43, folder 680.
      - IK 141 Maastricht with its Fortifications. Paris: Le Rouge., 1747
        Map tab inscription: 1747/Mastrich/IK/141.
        Inscribed on map: plan de Mastricht